<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.soft.SoftwareFeatureSets">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>SoftwareFeatureSets describe the groups of SoftwareCommands that distinguish a particular release of Software. The SoftwareCommands contained in the SoftwareFeatureSets are programmable by a particular PartyRole (e.g., a Developer, or NetworkOperator, and in rare cases and EndUser).    Often, SoftwareFeatureSets are used by the manufacturer to define a custom or semi-custom build of software, or are provided as a set of options that are orderable by the Customer.    This should not be confused with Capabilities. Capabilities define what features and functions are available at a given moment for the Resource. Thus, SoftwareFeatureSets represent groups of commands that are available in a device, whereas Capabilities represent higher-level generic functions available in a Resource. For exampe, the ability to perform BGP routing is a Capability, whereas the actual commands used to implement BGP routing are SoftwareCommands that reside in one or more SoftwareFeatureSets. Hence, SoftwareFeatureSets may or may not offer BGP as a programmable feature.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{ed347231-d00c-4c99-8860-de2646294000}</guid>
  <label>SoftwareFeatureSets</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.soft.SoftwareFeatureSets</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.soft.SoftwareFeatureSets</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>