<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PXPEnforcementDetails">  <container>true</container>  <description><![CDATA[    <p>This class implements the semantics of the EnforcesExecutionOf association. This association defines the set of PolicyEnforcementPoints whose actions are enforced by this PolicyEnforcementPoint.This association defines the set of PolicyExecutionPoints whose actions are enforced by a particular PolicyEnforcementPoint.    In contrast to the DirectsExecution association, the cardinality of this association is 1..n on both sides. Each side is 1..n because all PolicyExecutionPoints must have at least one associated PolicyEnforcementPoint, but may have more (if, for example, different PolicyEnforcementPoints are used for different functions that are controlled in a PolicyExecutionPoint). This ensure that the PolicyActions sent by a PolicyExecutionPoint can be checked (by the PolicyEnforcementPoint). Some PolicyEnforcementPoints, however, are capable of enforcing multiple PolicyExecutionPoints, and a PolicyEnforcementPoint is only relevant if it enforces the actions of a PolicyExecutionPoint.</p>                <p>This association class  is  optional</p>  ]]></description>  <guid>{ffc605ec-24dc-4b36-9096-410d00b8fb5d}</guid>  <label>PXPEnforcementDetails</label>  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>  <xmlMap type="xmap">    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>  </xmlMap>  <childList>    <child name="pxpEnforcementRequestTimePeriod" type="dstruct">      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This attribute defines the start and end times (in the form of time stamps) in which this PolicyEnforcementPoint must enforce the actions taken by this PolicyExecutionPoint.</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dstruct_tip.cbe.base.TimePeriod</element>      <guid>{6e8fe345-2bc3-4c44-b681-a9abc1f685dd}</guid>      <label>pxpEnforcementRequestTimePeriod</label>    </child>    <child name="pxpEnforcementCommMethod" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This is an enumerated integer that defines the communication method used between this PolicyExecutionPoint and this PolicyEnforcementPoint. Values include:        0: Not yet established        1: Telnet        2: COPS        3: Proprietary Protocol</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>      <guid>{cec87c88-12d9-442d-bc1e-4dc6aedf0def}</guid>      <label>pxpEnforcementCommMethod</label>    </child>  </childList>  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PXPEnforcementDetails</element>    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>    <variableList>      <variable name="model" type="uivar">        <label>model</label>        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PXPEnforcementDetails</valueType>      </variable>    </variableList>    <vformList>      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>      </vform>    </vformList>  </UserInterface></dataStructure>