<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PEPDirectionDetails">  <container>true</container>  <description><![CDATA[    <p>This class implements the semantics of the DirectsEnforcementOf association. This association defines the set of PolicyEnforcementPoints that are managed by this PolicyDecisionPoint.This association defines the set of PolicyEnforcementPoints that a given PolicyDecisionPoint can direct.    The semantics of this association are implemented using the PEPDirectionsDetails association class.    The cardinality of this association is 1 on the PolicyDecisionPoint side and 1..n on the PolicyEnforcementPoint side. This means that a PolicyDecisionPoint can provide decisions for one or more PolicyEnforcementPoint (note that without a PolicyEnforcementPoint a PolicyDecisionPoint is useless). However, if multiple PolicyDecisionPoints are allowed to tell a given PolicyEnforcementPoint what to do, then there is no guarantee that the PolicyDecisionPoints won't conflict with each other. Thus, there can only be one PolicyDecisionPoint for a given PolicyEnforcementPoint.</p>                <p>This association class  is  optional</p>  ]]></description>  <guid>{84a7a7bf-2fee-4e44-94df-a43c63028eb5}</guid>  <label>PEPDirectionDetails</label>  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>  <xmlMap type="xmap">    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>  </xmlMap>  <childList>    <child name="pepRequestTimePeriod" type="dstruct">      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This attribute defines the start and end times (in the form of time stamps) in which this PolicyDecisionPoint is allowed to manage this set of PolicyEnforcementPoints.</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dstruct_tip.cbe.base.TimePeriod</element>      <guid>{5d3fa929-0c44-4d25-a08c-1e63aed67ef8}</guid>      <label>pepRequestTimePeriod</label>    </child>    <child name="pepCommMethod" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This is an enumerated integer that defines the communication method used between this PolicyDecisionPoint and this PolicyEnforcementPoint. Values include:        0: Not yet established        1: Telnet        2: COPS        3: Proprietary Protocol</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>      <guid>{a384aba0-34ec-4a94-9afe-a2470e13dc12}</guid>      <label>pepCommMethod</label>    </child>  </childList>  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PEPDirectionDetails</element>    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>    <variableList>      <variable name="model" type="uivar">        <label>model</label>        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.appli.server.PEPDirectionDetails</valueType>      </variable>    </variableList>    <vformList>      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>      </vform>    </vformList>  </UserInterface></dataStructure>