<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmk.ContainedPolicySetsDetail">  <container>true</container>  <description><![CDATA[    <p>This class represents the semantics of the ContainedPolicySets aggregation. It provides additional semantics that enable this grouping of PolicySets to be prioritized and enabled, so that they can interwork with other PolicyRules and PolicyGroups. Note that each object in this aggregation must have the exact same decision strategy.This aggregation is used to gather together discrete PolicySet objects to form a group of PolicySet objects. Such a group must share the same DecisionStrategy.</p>                <p>This association class  is  optional</p>  ]]></description>  <guid>{a623315d-0169-4a28-83fd-62f6d266b5b2}</guid>  <label>ContainedPolicySetsDetail</label>  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>  <xmlMap type="xmap">    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>  </xmlMap>  <childList>    <child name="enabled" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This is an enumerated integer. If its value is 1 (which means enabled), then this signifies that this object is enabled for evaluation. If its value is 3 (which means that it is enabled for debugging), then this rule can be used in test or debug scenarios. If its value is 2, then this object is disabled and cannot be used or evaluated.        Note that this object still might end up being disabled, even if this attribute is TRUE. For example, an associated PolicyTimePeriodCondition might evaluate to FALSE, effectively disabling this object. That's why the phrasing said "enabled for evaluation" instead of "enabled for use".        Values include:        0: Unknown        1: Enabled for evaluation        2: Disabled for use        3: Enabled for debugging</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>      <guid>{a3b736dd-a555-492e-b193-5a8147abd6a8}</guid>      <label>enabled</label>    </child>    <child name="priority" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This attribute is a non-negative integer that is used to prioritize PolicyRules among each other, and/or PolicyGroups that are contained within a PolicyRule. Larger integer values indicate higher priority        Priorities apply to PolicySets (e.g., PolicyGroups and PolicyRules) and are to be used at the same level of scoping. That is, if a PolicyGroup contains n PolicyGroups or PolicyRules, the priority of the outermost (or parent) PolicyGroup can be compared with either stand-alone PolicyRules or PolicyGroups (at that same level of nesting).        The default setting of this attribute is zero.        Prioritization among policy rules provides a basic mechanism for resolving policy conflicts.</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>      <guid>{c3c31c25-4b9d-462c-b135-e28b3d7a1a96}</guid>      <label>priority</label>    </child>  </childList>  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmk.ContainedPolicySetsDetail</element>    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>    <variableList>      <variable name="model" type="uivar">        <label>model</label>        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmk.ContainedPolicySetsDetail</valueType>      </variable>    </variableList>    <vformList>      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>      </vform>    </vformList>  </UserInterface></dataStructure>