<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.cpd.CompoundResourceSpecComposite">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is a concrete class for describing specific attributes, behavior, relationships, constraints, and semantics for building composite CompoundResource objects. The purpose of this class is to be able to track specifications of CompoundResources separately from other types of ResourceSpecifications. Note that this class inherits the ModifiesResourceSpec aggregation, and therefore can be used with the corresponding CompoundResource class.    The key difference between a CompoundResourceSpec and either a PhysicalResourceSpec and a LogicalResourceSpec is that a PhysicalResourceSpec and LogicalResourceSpec define templates for specifying the invariant characteristics and behavior of PhysicalResources and LogicalResources, respectively. In contrast, a CompoundResourceSpec is used to describe templates that contain at least one PhysicalResourceSpec and at least one LogicalResourceSpec. Optionally, one or more CompoundResourceSpecs may also be specified.    The difference between a CompoundResourceSpecAtomic entity and a CompoundResourceSpecComposite entity is that a CompoundResourceSpecAtomic entity is designed to be a stand-alone entity. (Note that it still aggregates at least one PhysicalResourceSpec and at least one LogicalResourceSpec; however, the end result is that this CompoundResourceSpecAtomic entity can be used by itself.) In contrast, a CompoundResourceSpecComposite entity is made up of one or more CompoundResourceSpecs, one of which must be a CompoundResourceSpecAtomic entity.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{7ff6ea20-a1f1-4dcc-b110-bea6eaff0543}</guid>
  <label>CompoundResourceSpecComposite</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="compoundResourceSpec" type="dstruct">
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p></p>                                <p>This element is generated from an association end.</p>                                <p>This association end  has  multiplicity *</p>                                <p>This association end  has  aggregation none</p>                                <p>This association end  is  navigable</p>                                <p>This association end  is  an end of association HasCompoundResourceSpecs</p>                                <p>This association end  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.cpd.ArrayOfCompoundResourceSpec</element>
      <guid>{77dafa2c-0f15-4f96-9f13-955c5fe4084e}</guid>
      <label>compoundResourceSpec</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.cpd.CompoundResourceSpecComposite</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.cpd.CompoundResourceSpecComposite</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>