<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.itf.ATMInterface">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>ATM, orr Asynchronous Transfer Mode, is a network technology based on transferring data in cells of a fixed size. The cell used with ATM is relatively small compared to that used with older technologies. In principle, the small, constant cell size allows ATM equipment to transmit video, audio, and computer data over the same network, and assure that no single type of data can dominate network traffic.    ATM creates a fixed route between two points whenever data transfer begins. This differs from TCP/IP, in which messages are divided into packets and each packet can take a different route from source to destination. This difference makes it easier to track and bill data usage across an ATM network, but it makes it less adaptable to sudden surges in network traffic.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{581bcba3-68a3-48c7-9c73-d7783da10ed7}</guid>
  <label>ATMInterface</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="bitRateType" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an enumerated integer, and defines the transmission philosophy used. Values include:        0: not yet configured        1: constant bit rate (CBR)        2: variable bit rate (VBR)        3: available bit rate (ABR)        4: unspecified bit rate (UBR)        CBR specifies a fixed bit rate so that data is sent in a steady stream. This is analogous to a leased line.        VBR provides a specified throughput capacity but data is not sent evenly. This is often used for voice and video data.        ABR provides a guaranteed minimum capacity but allows data to be bursted at higher capacities when the network is free.        UBR does not guarantee any throughput levels. This is used for applications, such as file transfer, that can tolerate delays.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{116de7ab-1bf2-4e6b-a17a-0ba09e3f6e20}</guid>
      <label>bitRateType</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.itf.ATMInterface</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.itf.ATMInterface</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>