<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.PolicyConditionComposite">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>The PolicyConditionComposite class is designed to be an intelligent container. The PolicyConditionComposite class is the base class for all complex policy conditions. A complex policy condition consists of an aggregation of PolicyConditionAtomic and/or PolicyConditionComposite objects, which in turn form a complex Boolean statement. It is important to note that such an object still evaluates to a single Boolean TRUE or FALSE value.    Conceptually, this is a stand-alone object that consists of one PolicyCondition that provides an overall context for either a nested or a group of subordinate PolicyConditions to be evaluated.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{1ad96d2d-552b-478d-ae66-577cdddf2e3b}</guid>
  <label>PolicyConditionComposite</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="conditionIsCNF" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a Boolean attribute that, if TRUE, defines the condition clause of this PolicyConditionComposite object to be represented in Conjunctive Normal Form (e.g., an And of Ors). If the value of this attribute is FALSE, then the condition clause will be represented in Disjunctive Normal Form.        This attribute controls the setting of how multiple condition clauses (as represented by individual PolicyConditionAtomic objects) are treated in the PolicyConditionComposite object. As such, it is different from the attribute PolicyRule.IsCNF, which controls how multiple PolicyConditionComposite objects are treated in a PolicyRule object.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Boolean</element>
      <guid>{be0f4a33-0ba6-4e23-a424-12a66c09fcdf}</guid>
      <label>conditionIsCNF</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.PolicyConditionComposite</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.PolicyConditionComposite</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>