<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.ContainedPolicyConditionDetails">  <container>true</container>  <description><![CDATA[    <p>This is a class that implements the semantics needed for the PolicyConditionInPolicyCondition aggregation. This aggregation defines the set of PolicyConditions that are contained in this PolicyCondition.    Note that the ContainedPolicyConditionDetails class and the PolicyConditionRuleDetails class have conceptually the same attributes. This is because they both provide semantics to form a condition expression. The difference lies in their placement relative to the PolicyRule class. That is, the ContainedPolicyConditionDetails class is used to combine individual expressions within a condition clause, whereas the PolicyConditionRuleDetails class is used to describe how the completed condition clause appears to the PolicyRule. These attributes are described in the Data Dictionary section of this Addendum.    This aggregation is used for two distinct purposes. First, it is used to gather together discrete PolicyConditions to form a PolicyCondition clause. In this usage, the set of individual PolicyConditionAtomic objects are aggregated by a PolicyConditionComposite object.    The second use is to form compound PolicyConditions. In this case, the PolicyConditionAtomic object aggregates PolicyConditionAtomic and/or PolicyConditionComposite objects. The former provides a simple nested PolicyCondition, while the latter provides structure for grouping the sub-conditions that are dependent on a higher-level condition.</p>                <p>This association class  is  optional</p>  ]]></description>  <guid>{2fb3781d-a95b-4fe1-b712-b53c550f1bb4}</guid>  <label>ContainedPolicyConditionDetails</label>  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>  <xmlMap type="xmap">    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>  </xmlMap>  <childList>    <child name="containedConditionIsNegated" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This is a Boolean attribute that, if TRUE, signifies that this condition term is negated. The default value for this attribute is FALSE.</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Boolean</element>      <guid>{5a256ad0-deaa-4fc6-b0fa-436884c54f82}</guid>      <label>containedConditionIsNegated</label>    </child>    <child name="containedConditionGroupNumber" type="dstruct">      <datatype>true</datatype>      <description><![CDATA[        <p>This attribute is used to define the group to which the condition is a part of. It corresponds logical to the position of parentheses used to group condition terms together.</p>                          <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                          <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>      ]]></description>      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>      <guid>{352ad46b-b258-4fe1-b0a3-b6ad3d819f18}</guid>      <label>containedConditionGroupNumber</label>    </child>  </childList>  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.ContainedPolicyConditionDetails</element>    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>    <variableList>      <variable name="model" type="uivar">        <label>model</label>        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.cond.ContainedPolicyConditionDetails</valueType>      </variable>    </variableList>    <vformList>      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>      </vform>    </vformList>  </UserInterface></dataStructure>