<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.phy.device.PhysicalDeviceComposite">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is a concrete base class for representing hardware devices that can be managed that contains one or more sub-ordinate devices. In other words, this physical device is not a stand-alone physical device; rather, it represents an aggregation of physical devices. Each physical device in this aggregation can be managed.    This class represents a convenient aggregation point for combining different aspects of a device (e.g., its physical composition as well as the set of services that it offers). It also enables the device itself to have a physical manifestation. Examples of this class include routers and switches, computers, and other end-devices that are managed.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{dd560c09-1865-4537-8dab-177b0786fdd4}</guid>
  <label>PhysicalDeviceComposite</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="numberOfDevicesTotal" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This attribute defines the total number of PhysicalDevices aggregated by this PhysicalDeviceComposite object. Note that this aggregation is for that particular level of aggregation. Thus, if a PhysicalDeviceComposite, called A, contains another PhysicalDeviceComposite, called B, then B's instance of this attribute will define how many PhysicalDevices are aggregated by B, whereas A's instance of this attribute will defined how many PhysicalDevices are aggregated by A (which includes those aggregated by B).</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{2e5941e3-0471-415a-97c2-f31f0ba1f8ff}</guid>
      <label>numberOfDevicesTotal</label>
    </child>
    <child name="numberOfDevicesCurrent" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This attribute defines the current number of PhysicalDevices aggregated by this PhysicalDeviceComposite object that are active and manageable.        Note that this aggregation is for that particular level of aggregation. Thus, if a PhysicalDeviceComposite, called A, contains another PhysicalDeviceComposite, called B, then B's instance of this attribute will define how many PhysicalDevices are aggregated by B, whereas A's instance of this attribute will defined how many PhysicalDevices are aggregated by A (which includes those aggregated by B).</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{942962f1-a7f8-45c6-ac89-20b5648049e0}</guid>
      <label>numberOfDevicesCurrent</label>
    </child>
    <child name="physicalDevice" type="dstruct">
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p></p>                                <p>This element is generated from an association end.</p>                                <p>This association end  has  multiplicity *</p>                                <p>This association end  has  aggregation none</p>                                <p>This association end  is  navigable</p>                                <p>This association end  is  an end of association HasDevices</p>                                <p>This association end  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.phy.device.ArrayOfPhysicalDevice</element>
      <guid>{9665e3b2-601a-4039-8b93-330ef6e19151}</guid>
      <label>physicalDevice</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.phy.device.PhysicalDeviceComposite</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.phy.device.PhysicalDeviceComposite</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>