<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyConditionVendor">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is a concrete base class that provides a general extension mechanism for representing PolicyConditions that have not been modeled with the attributes specified in this model. This class uses two of its properties (constraintData and constraintEncoding) for defining the content and format of a vendor-specific condition. Its other two attributes are used to describe the type of condition that this represents, and to provide a standard definition of a TRUE or FALSE response. This latter enables this object to interoperate with other PolicyVariableStandard objects as part of a PolicyConditon clause.    Standardized extensions are not expected to use this class.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{8b5ec8be-8696-49ac-ba9d-649ab7357428}</guid>
  <label>PolicyConditionVendor</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="constraintEncoding" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>The constraintEncoding attribute is a string that is used to represent an OID that in turn identifies the encoding and semantics of the constraintData attribute in this instance.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{a7385975-1854-471b-8123-fd16dccc957c}</guid>
      <label>constraintEncoding</label>
    </child>
    <child name="conditionType" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a free-form string that can be used to define the type of condition that this instance is checking.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{83eee471-cf10-4c09-9dd8-f42a356dda8c}</guid>
      <label>conditionType</label>
    </child>
    <child name="conditionResponse" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a Boolean attribute that is used to allow a 'standard' definition of a TRUE/FALSE response to be made by an external system attached to the model at this point. This will allow integration with a generalized policy processing engine.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Boolean</element>
      <guid>{752104da-cd58-4dc0-bbc5-a469c382572f}</guid>
      <label>conditionResponse</label>
    </child>
    <child name="constraintData" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>The constraintData attribute is a string that provides a general extension mechanism for representing PolicyConditions that have not been modeled with specific attributes (as specified in this model). The format of this attribute is determined by the OID value stored in the constraintEncoding attribute of this class. The constraintEncoding attribute provides a convenient and simple mechanism by which a Policy Server can determine whether it supports the values stored in an instance of constraintData. If it doesn't recognize any of the OID values in the constraintEncoding attribute, then it will not know how to interpret the data in the corresponding constraintData attributes. The action for the policy decision point to take in case it does not recognize the format of this data could itself be modeled as a PolicyRule, governing the behavior of the Policy Server.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{443e92fe-3174-4520-a08b-955d1ab52064}</guid>
      <label>constraintData</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyConditionVendor</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyConditionVendor</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>