<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyVariable">
  <abstract>true</abstract>
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is an abstract class for modeling different types of variables that can be used to form a PolicyStatement. The variable specifies an attribute or concept that should either be matched or in some way compared to a value when the condition is evaluated.    There are three important factors that must be taken into account in the design of variables. The first is that not every combination of a variable and a value creates a meaningful condition. For example, port numbers cannot be negative. Rather, the type of variable in the condition defines the set of matchable value types.    Second, just because a value has the correct datatype does not mean that it can be meaningfully compared to a variable. To continue the above example, a port of 1,000,000 is meaningless. This is handled in this model by specifying constraints (using OCL) that apply to a particular variable that must be obeyed by any value that it is being compared to. The ExpectedPolicyValuesForVariable association binds a PolicyVariable to a PolicyValue; any constraints that are required in this binding are added to an instance of this association using OCL.    Third, while the DEN-ng model defines a set of useful PolicyVariables, there is a high likelihood that specific applications will need extensions to these variables. This is accommodated through the notion of implicit and explicit PolicyVariable classes.</p>                <p>This entity  is  abstract</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{948fc646-70dd-44c6-bf1b-610f6a256a7c}</guid>
  <label>PolicyVariable</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="policyOperator" type="dstruct">
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p></p>                                <p>This element is generated from an association end.</p>                                <p>This association end  has  multiplicity 0..*</p>                                <p>This association end  has  aggregation none</p>                                <p>This association end  is  navigable</p>                                <p>This association end  is  an end of association OperatorConstraintDetails</p>                                <p>This association end  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.stat.ArrayOfPolicyOperator</element>
      <guid>{9f37a5a7-3bd1-45c5-a108-bac5c3eeeff6}</guid>
      <label>policyOperator</label>
    </child>
    <child name="policyValue" type="dstruct">
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p></p>                                <p>This element is generated from an association end.</p>                                <p>This association end  has  multiplicity 0..*</p>                                <p>This association end  has  aggregation none</p>                                <p>This association end  is  navigable</p>                                <p>This association end  is  an end of association ValueConstraintDetails</p>                                <p>This association end  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct.val.ArrayOfPolicyValue</element>
      <guid>{7788a9a8-8e76-4ea0-92fd-65b0ba14a728}</guid>
      <label>policyValue</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyVariable</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.struct._var.PolicyVariable</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>