<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.os.VendorNetworkDeviceOS">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is an abstract base class for representing software. The HasSoftware association is used to define software that is associated in some way with a ManagedPhysicalEntity, such as programs and operating systems. Since this software can be associated with complete devices or components of device, this association is defined between the roots of the two classes.    Currently, the subclasses of this class reflect user-facing features (e.g., features that are manageable, configurable, and executable by users and applications).</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{82d034b1-4f2d-4103-ae64-bc132098dbe7}</guid>
  <label>VendorNetworkDeviceOS</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="releaseStatus" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This attribute is an enumerated integer that defines the particualr release status of this software. Values include:        0: alpha        1. beta        2: FCS (First Customer Shipment)        3. GD (General Deployment)        4: SV (Special Version for 1 or more customers)        5: EOE (end of engineering)        6: EOS (end of sale)        7: EOL (end of life)        FCS marks the beginning of the limited deployment phase. In this phase, the software is usually certified on a few platforms but not all platforms.        GD marks the certification of stable software on all major platforms.        SV is a special build for a particular customer that needs special fixes or features.        EOE means that no new engineering fixes will be applied, but the software can still be ordered. EOS means that the software can no longer be ordered, but will still be supported. EOL means that the software can no longer be supported, and cannot be ordered.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{086f32b2-8aea-4a5b-b59b-7a91a8b8999d}</guid>
      <label>releaseStatus</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.os.VendorNetworkDeviceOS</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.res.log.os.VendorNetworkDeviceOS</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>