<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.service.serv.rfs.CoS2Bundle">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This class represents the Class of Service settings for a specific ServiceBundle. ServiceBundles are related to ServicePackages via the packageContainsServiceBundles aggregation. Thus, this enables different CoS settings to be associated with a ServicePackage, which is what the Customer buys.    This version of the DEN-ng Service model defines four exemplary subclasses of ServiceBundle for defining four different groups of Class of Service (CoS). The idea is to use each CoSBundle class to represent the Class of Service settings for a specific ServiceBundle. This enables different CoS settings to be associated with the different CustomerFacingServices that are defined by a particular ServicePackage, which is what the Customer buys. For example, CoS1 could be used for VoIP, CoS2 could be used for mission-critical applications, CoS3 could be used for all other applications that are not mission-critical but require better than best-effort delivery, and CoS4 could define best effort service delivery.    Please see the DEN-ng Service model for more details. In the DEN-ng white paper, this is asociated with QoS needed for mission-critical non-voice applications such as SAP or ERP.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{09ae91ed-9443-4bec-970b-b97a1a1622d0}</guid>
  <label>CoS2Bundle</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.service.serv.rfs.CoS2Bundle</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.service.serv.rfs.CoS2Bundle</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>