<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.phy.PhysicalResourceSpecAtomic">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>A PhysicalResourceSpecAtomic class is a concrete class for describing specific attributes, behavior, relationships, constraints, and semantics for building PhysicalResource objects. The purpose of this class is to be able to track PhysicalResourceSpecifications separately from other types of ResourceSpecifications. Note that this class inherits the SpecifiesResource aggregation, and therefore can be used with the corresponding PhysicalResource class.    The difference between this class and the PhysicalResourceSpecComposite class is that this class represents stand-alone PhysicalResourceSpecifications. The PhysicalResourceSpecComposite class represents a specification that is in reality made up of a set (usually a hierarchy) of PhysicalResourceSpecifications.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{fcf7d77f-5496-42b4-92e9-d721328681ab}</guid>
  <label>PhysicalResourceSpecAtomic</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="modelNumber" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a string that represents a manufacturer-allocated number used to identify the general type and/or category of the hardware item. This, in combination with the PartNumber and the VendorName, identify different types of hardware items. The SerialNumber can then be used to differentiate between different instances of the same type of hardware item. This is an optional attribute.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{e3f23adb-d9cb-43ce-931d-a76fcd73b320}</guid>
      <label>modelNumber</label>
    </child>
    <child name="partNumber" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a string that defines a manufacturer-allocated part number assigned by the organization that manufactures the hardware item. This, in combination with the ModelNumber and the VendorName, identify different types of hardware items. The SerialNumber can then be used to differentiate between different instances of the same type of hardware item. This is a REQUIRED attribute.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{f6bbe401-27e7-4de4-92c5-99f7e4516847}</guid>
      <label>partNumber</label>
    </child>
    <child name="skuNumber" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a string that defines the manufacturer-allocated Stock Keeping Unit (SKU) number of the hardware item. This is an optional attribute.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{2247bfa5-1177-486c-a608-f42c5d8ee76e}</guid>
      <label>skuNumber</label>
    </child>
    <child name="vendorName" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is a string that defines the name of the manufacturer. This, in combination with the ModelNumber and the PartNumber, identify different types of hardware items. The SerialNumber can then be used to differentiate between different instances of the same type of hardware item. This is a REQUIRED attribute.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{70032139-97b4-404b-9075-a843b27d4d81}</guid>
      <label>vendorName</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.phy.PhysicalResourceSpecAtomic</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.resource.spec.phy.PhysicalResourceSpecAtomic</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>