<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<dataStructure name="sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmkspec.PolicyRuleSpec">
  <container>true</container>
  <description><![CDATA[
    <p>This is a concrete base class that is used to define the invariant characteristics (attributes, methods, constraints and relationships) of a PolicyRule entity.</p>                <p>This entity  is  optional</p>
  ]]></description>
  <extends>dstruct_tip.internal.entity.EntityBase</extends>
  <guid>{6b833103-76c3-4941-b44b-80adbc94f2e2}</guid>
  <label>PolicyRuleSpec</label>
  <metaVersion>4</metaVersion>
  <xmlMap type="xmap">
    <includeXsiType>true</includeXsiType>
  </xmlMap>
  <childList>
    <child name="policyActionSelectCriteria" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an attribute that contains an OCL expression to prescribe any limitations on the types of PolicyActions that can be used with any PolicyRules that are derived from this particular PolicyRuleSpec. This enables a PolicyRuleSpec to be built that defines what types of PolicyActions can be used to build PolicyRules. This in turn ensures that a given set of PolicyRules carry standard functionality.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{644d98f6-bcdc-40e8-8105-03abebdc2c74}</guid>
      <label>policyActionSelectCriteria</label>
    </child>
    <child name="policyConditionSelectCriteria" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an attribute that contains an OCL expression to prescribe any limitations on the types of PolicyConditions that can be used with any PolicyRules that are derived from this particular PolicyRuleSpec. This enables a PolicyRuleSpec to be built that defines what types of PolicyConditions can be used to build PolicyRules. This in turn ensures that a given set of PolicyRules carry standard functionality.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{e1eab817-3ea6-4edd-83a8-188fd878f2c5}</guid>
      <label>policyConditionSelectCriteria</label>
    </child>
    <child name="policyEventSelectCriteria" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an attribute that contains an OCL expression to prescribe any limitations on the types of PolicyEvents that can be used with any PolicyRules that are derived from this particular PolicyRuleSpec. This enables a PolicyRuleSpec to be built that defines what types of PolicyEvents can be used to trigger the evaluation of PolicyRules. This in turn ensures that a given set of PolicyRules carry standard functionality.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.String</element>
      <guid>{4b138c98-2437-4aaa-9543-c1ffbf762011}</guid>
      <label>policyEventSelectCriteria</label>
    </child>
    <child name="sequencedActions" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an enumerated integer defines how the ordering of the PolicyActions associated with this PolicyRule is to be interpreted.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{a867fa31-4504-4deb-817b-05727404b275}</guid>
      <label>sequencedActions</label>
    </child>
    <child name="executionStrategy" type="dstruct">
      <datatype>true</datatype>
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p>This is an enumerated integer that defines the strategy to be used when executing the sequenced actions aggregated by this PolicyRule. Defined execution strategies include:        0: Unknown        1: Do Until Success        2: Do All        3: Do Until Failure        4: Do All Without Failure or Do Nothing        "Do Until Success" means that actions should be executed according to their predefined order, until successful execution of a single action. At that point, the process should stop (even if there are additional actions that could be executed).        "Do All" means that all actions should be executed that are part of the set, according to their predefined order. This should continue, even if one or more of the actions fails.        "Do Until Failure" means that all actions should be executed according to their predefined order until an action fails to execute. At that point, the entire sequence should be stopped.        Finally, "Do All Without Failure or Do Nothing" means that all actions specified should be performed. However, if a failure occurs, then NONE of the actions should be performed. This implies EITHER the ability to look-ahead and ensure that the actions will be able to be performed successfully, or the ability to perform a rollback of that action and all previous actions when an error is encountered.</p>                                <p>This element is generated from an attribute.</p>                                <p>This attribute  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dtype_com.conceptwave.system.Integer</element>
      <guid>{86b941ea-b009-4cec-81c0-13fbb0ec694a}</guid>
      <label>executionStrategy</label>
    </child>
    <child name="policyRule" type="dstruct">
      <description><![CDATA[
        <p></p>                                <p>This element is generated from an association end.</p>                                <p>This association end  has  multiplicity *</p>                                <p>This association end  has  aggregation none</p>                                <p>This association end  is  navigable</p>                                <p>This association end  is  an end of association SpecifiesPolicyRule</p>                                <p>This association end  is  optional</p>
      ]]></description>
      <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmk.ent.ArrayOfPolicyRule</element>
      <guid>{b6e7660a-d506-4065-977b-e642ea978164}</guid>
      <label>policyRule</label>
    </child>
  </childList>
  <UserInterface name="UserInterface" type="tree">
    <defaultFolderImage>undefined</defaultFolderImage>
    <defaultLeafImage>undefined</defaultLeafImage>
    <element>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmkspec.PolicyRuleSpec</element>
    <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface</extends>
    <tableDoc>doc_com.conceptwave.system.TreeDocument</tableDoc>
    <variableList>
      <variable name="model" type="uivar">
        <label>model</label>
        <valueType>dstruct_sid.org.tmforum.tip.cbe.policy.fmkspec.PolicyRuleSpec</valueType>
      </variable>
    </variableList>
    <vformList>
      <vform name="Forms" type="frmui">
        <extends>tree_com.conceptwave.system.DataStructureUserInterface/frmui_Forms</extends>
      </vform>
    </vformList>
  </UserInterface>
</dataStructure>